layads.com 2011-12-29

# Publish Online Advertising in India | Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY

Layads.com Privacy Policy : 

Layads.com privacy describes how we handle personal information. We utilize safe, secure technology to protect your personally identifiable information that we collect and receive through our websites. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy and how we use and protect your personal information. 

Information Collection : 

Information posted on Layads.com is available to all. If you choose to share the Personal information you are agreeing for the transfer and storage of information you provided with us. The Information we collect and store would be of email address and physical contact information and also computer sign on data and also statistics on various page views along with IP Information which includes IP address and weblog information . 

Usage of Services : 

We value your trust and work hard to earn your confidence, so that you can enthusiastically use our services. We do not collect information from persons under the age of 18 with our knowledge. Persons under the age of 18 are not allowed to use our websites unsupervised. If you are under the age of 18, you may use our websites only in conjunction with and under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian. If we learn that a posting has been submitted by a person under the age of 18 without supervision that post/user will be removed. Be cautious layads.com never sends you mails for your username/password. 

Amending/Modification of Privacy Policy : 

We reserve the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. Any significant changes, to this Policy will be posted on our website. 

Cookies Information : 

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by layads.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by our advertisers. 

Disclosure of Information : 

Layads.com do not sell or rent your personal data to anyone. The personal data you provide us is saved in a secure environment and is kept in our records. Information collected is stored in a single database, accessible only by Layads.com members. We employ reasonable and current security methods and technologies in order to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information. We reserve the right to release information about our users in order to comply with the law. We may also release personal data to enforce or apply the terms and conditions of our services, or to protect the rights, property or safety or our websites, our users, or the general public. For any inquiries contact [support@layads.com](mailto:support@layads.com)
